The enemy isn't out there... it is within.
Recon is a war, thriller film directed by Robert Port.
Four American soldiers in WW2, after witnessing the vicious murder of an innocent civilian at the hands of
their platoon Sergeant, are sent on a reconnaissance/suicide mission led by a local partisan.
Marson, played by Alexander Ludwig.
Heisman, played by RJ Fetherstonhaugh.
Hopewell, played by Mitch Ainley.
Asch, played by Chris Brochu.
Walberg, played by Christopher Crema.
Angelo, played by Franco Nero.
Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon is a series of military tactical
shooter video games published by Ubisoft.
In the series, the player is in charge of a
fictional, newly conceived squad of U.S.
Army Special Forces soldiers from Delta Company, 1st Battalion, 5th
Special Forces Group (5th SFG) stationed at Fort Bragg.
Except for the "1st Battalion, 5th SFG" designation, this reconnaissance unit is entirely fictional,
as Special Forces Battalions currently only support three Companies (A, B and C).
They are often referred to as "the Ghosts".
Their role is like other real world special operations forces, in
that their operations are kept highly classified.
In Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon: Future Soldier, it is shown that the Ghost's unit has multiple designations and is part of JSOC; they are also known as the Group for
Specialized Tactics (or GST—where the term "Ghost" comes from), much like real JSOC units such as Delta Force (1st SFOD-D or CAG) and SEAL Team Six (or DEVGRU).
Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon has also been novelized by Grant
Blackwood under the pseudonym David Michaels.
As of 2025, over 40 million units have been sold.
The tone is intense.